
{"questions" : [ {"question": "Continental United States has 4 time zones, can you name them?",
  "correct": "D",
  "options":   [{
    "A":"IeBNxxc",
    "B":"HKWPIQo",
    "C":"GRYDTLc",
    "D":"Pacific, Mountain, Central, Eastern"
  }]},
  {"question": "What was the Turkish city of Istanbul called before 1930?",
    "correct": "B",
    "options": [{
      "A":"AYjcnVm",
      "B":"Constantinople",
      "C":"UFBxWtC",
      "D":"NJypGDM"}]},
  {"question": "From which US city do the band The Killers originate?",
    "correct": "B",
    "options": [{
      "A":"psyDjMj",
      "B":"Las Vegas" ,
      "C":"FOVKlDm" ,
      "D": "bhcjksm"}]},
  {"question": "Name the Coffee shop in US sitcom Friends",
    "correct": "A",
    "options": [{
      "A": "Central Perk",
      "B": "ayXpXdp",
      "C": "koQgEgz",
      "D": "ufUXucl"}]},
  {"question": "How many human players are there on each side in a polo match?",
    "correct": "C",
    "options": [{
      "A": "iNMqUBU",
      "B": "CwKuCiv",
      "C": "Four",
      "D": "mNfMCOQ"}]},
  {"question": "In what year did Tony Blair become British Prime Minister?",
    "correct": "D",
    "options": [{
      "A": "WpNPAZp",
      "B": "Zrepumo",
      "C": "dpdiXxC",
      "D": "1997"}]},
  {"question": "How many times has England won the men\u2019s football World Cup?",
    "correct": "B",
    "options": [{
      "A":"etrKbIX",
      "B":"Once (1966)",
      "C":"jWpjJQJ",
      "D":"sRoDsbn"}]},
  {"question": "What is the capital of New Zealand?",
    "correct": "A",
    "options": [{
      "A":"Once (1966)",
      "B":"PoXHdLQ",
      "C":"uCSdjoJ",
      "D":"hbXbUfW"}]},
  {"question": "Street artist Banksy is originally associated with which British city?",
    "correct": "C",
    "options": [{
      "A":"HdubprE",
      "B":"vHDSiCg",
      "C":"Bristol",
      "D":"AoWoEzH"}]},
  {"question": "From what grain is the Japanese spirit Sake made?",
    "correct": "Rice",
    "options": ["nBgFMmm", "mdsiYgC", "toDrXny"]},
  {"question": "In which part of your body would you find the cruciate ligament?",
    "correct": "Knee",
    "options": ["MeHNoip",  "IqEufkM",  "gTYBGEQ"]},
  {"question": "What is the name of the main antagonist in the Shakespeare play Othello?",
    "correct": "Iago",
    "options": ["dXjTmdQ",  "mvxzwuT",  "DemLTCA"]},
  {"question": "What element is denoted by the chemical symbol Sn in the periodic table?",
    "correct": "Tin",
    "options": ["WmXgTHy",  "GfcByTK", "dfQdHYV"]},
  {"question": "What is the name of the 1976 film about the Watergate scandal, starring Robert Redford and Dustin Hoffman?",
    "correct": "All the President\u2019s Men",
    "options": ["bDUdLPw",  "XEvGAKO", "eRCytVF"]},
  {"question": "How many of Henry VIII\u2019s wives were called Catherine?",
    "correct": "3",
    "options": ["xgmuHMM",  "iboSdxk",  "qSpcPNT"]},
  {"question": "What was the most popular girls name in the UK in 2019?",
    "correct": "Olivia",
    "options": ["AUUKXnj",  "ksxaSxW",  "xPSjVDj"]},
  {"question": "Which comedian was the second permanent host of Never Mind the Buzzcocks after Mark Lamarr?",
    "correct": "Simon Amstell",
    "options": ["AVVqIZb",  "bQsVDhC",  "MdWbWYS"]},
  {"question": "Which popular video game franchise has released games with the subtitles World At War and Black Ops?",
    "correct": "Call of Duty",
    "options": ["qrnQyGR",  "njOcgJZ",  "uMIYHwt"]},
  {"question": "In what US State is the city Nashville?",
    "correct": "Tennessee",
    "options": ["KudnVjS",  "LbxXrxV",  "tMoHifN"]},
  {"question": "Which rock band was founded by Trent Reznor in 1988?",
    "correct": "Nine Inch Nails",
    "options": ["ahRktRD", "yJnOakB",  "KTndCpq"]},
  {"question": "What is the currency of Denmark?",
    "correct": "Krone",
    "options": ["Dgyhroe",  "VdCoupD",  "wbNuRAM"]},
  {"question": "Which Tennis Grand Slam is played on a clay surface?",
    "correct": "The French Open (Roland Garros)",
    "options": ["nAlZfsq", "nkFdCRN", "LKmxqeo"]},
  {"question": "In which European country would you find the Rijksmuseum?",
    "correct": "Netherlands",
    "options": ["GvGdRVm",  "TWWUYVW",  "cZlJoGz"]},
  {"question": "How many films have Al Pacino and Robert De Niro appeared in together?",
    "correct": "Four (The Godfather Part 2, Heat, Righteous Kill, The Irishman)",
    "options": ["WqpqENe",  "ByRPQRz",  "DUEGjIK"]},
  {"question": "What was the old name for a Snickers bar before it changed in 1990?",
    "correct": "Marathon",
    "options": ["beXCwAl",  "MBcYYCE",  "FulGAml"]},
  {"question": "Who was the head of state in Japan during the second world war?",
    "correct": "Emperor Hirohito",
    "options": ["ZVlswbz",  "qRtThEi", "dNqknWX"]},
  {"question": "What is the smallest planet in our solar system?",
    "correct": "Mercury",
    "options": ["BqyVyOT",  "qlkFGWT", "IAJyJnf"]},
  {"question": "Who wrote the novels Gone Girl and Sharp Objects?",
    "correct": "Gillian Flynn",
    "options": ["AmESfno", "VCtrceK", "DNFYUpS"]},
  {"question": "Which legendary surrealist artist is famous for painting melting clocks?",
    "correct": "Salvador Dali",
    "options": ["OAyzvuc", "jrCkooM",  "amaAlZs"]},
  {"question": "Which football club plays its home games at Loftus Road",
    "correct": "Queen\u2019s Park Rangers",
    "options": ["Eugzzsp", "GSJPDQu", "qxGKGMg"]}
]}
